

# PERSONAL DETAILS

Name	Danish Shaik	
D.O.B	27 August 1997	
Web	http://www.dshaik.com	
Contact	+1(408) 207-8836	
Email	✓ shaik.danish97@gmail.com	

# EDUCATION

High School	Monta Vista High School
Middle College	De-Anza College
<b>AWARDS</b>	
Third Place	Photo Hack Day (iMaze)-Featured on TechCrunch
Finalist	Brim (Outside Hacks)



### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Flipboard**

Jul 2014 - Sept 2014

# Softech

Jun 2013 - Aug 2013

## dshaik.com

Jan 2012 - May 2013



## **PROJECTS**

## **Reading Rainbow**

A native Mac application, which allows students to stream textbooks, and novels for free instantly. Reading Rainbow streams torrent files from kickass.so in order to allow students to access course material without paying money. Reading Rainbow the equivalent of Popcorn-Time for books.



#### **PROFILE**



- 📝 twitter.com/danshaik
- behance.net/jonnyevans
- (in) linkedin.com/in/danishshaik

Hello! I'm Danish, a 17 year old web developer based in Cupertino, CA.

I love coding, designing, ping pong, and working on neat projects. I attend De Anza College, through a Middle College Program taking college level courses as a senior in High School.

## **Engineering Intern**

Worked as a Software Developer Intern on the Platforms Team. Used several external and internal frameworks to build an internal analytics dashboard. Worked on an internal interface to increase productivity of customer-support team. An interface for dealing with customer issues and flagged items coupled with a robust analytics system with notifications and warnings.

## Web Dev Intern

Worked as a Software Engineering Intern on Web Development Team. Worked on Front-End for Company web presence. Used technologies include jOuery, Bootstrap, and Backbone.js to create a seamless beautiful responsive webpage.

## Freelance Developer

Met with clients to define aesthetic and functional specifications. Analyzed client's business objectives and directions for the web in terms of product positioning, branding, target audience or markets and web traffic generation. Worked with a variety of businesses in order to create a web presence for their brand.

#### Bash

Bash is a mobile application that makes organizing activities with friends seamless and hassle free. Bash lets you create an event and then immediately sends a push notification to all of the invited friends. Your friends can then opt in or opt out, without having to argue for hours on details.



## SKILLS



#### Languages

JavaScript HTML CSS3 C++



## Frameworks

Express.js d3.js jQuery Backbone.js Angular.js Bootstrap Foundation



#### **Technologies**

Node.js Jade EJS (Embedded JavaScript)



## **Platforms**

Web Chrome App Store Leap Motion